TAYLOR BERRY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Mobile: 208-484-2107 taylorberry019@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/taylormberry/ https://github.com/tberry019 Boise, ID.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Enthusiastic professional with a strong work ethic and lively attitude. Excited to conquer new opportunities and lead a successful team to carve our place within the company. Confident that my honed skills, and personal experiences mixed with my love for working with people will materialize into a collaborative team of innovation with a healthy work dynamic that reflects the core values of this company.

SPECIALIZATIONS

- C++
- Node.js
- Vue.js
- Javascript
- MongoDb
- Auth0
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- HTML5

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Certified ScrumMaster 2021 Scrum Alliance - 001263052

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Nov 2021 - Mar 2022 (Expected)
Boise CodeWorks, Boise, ID

Bachelors of Science University of Idaho, Idaho

WORK EXPERIENCE

Escrow Assistant/Funder Jan 2021 - Sep 2021 TitleOne Corporation, Boise, ID

Presented loan documents and other records for signing and returned loan

documents to lender after signing and following up on funding conditions.

- Reviewed real estate purchase contracts, ensuring they are complete and requesting any missing information.
- Performed preliminary audits and determined or obtained any necessary items to

clear a title.

- Prepared estimated closing statements for officer to review.
- Maintained files, recording appropriate documentation, sent checks once closing

was complete and transmitted documents to the lender.

Accounting Assistant Jul 2015 - Jan 2021 TitleOne Corporation, Boise, ID

 Applied principles of accounting to prepare, scope, and manage financial projects.

transactions, and budgeting reports across all areas of the company.

 Verified and approved outgoing wire transfers for all trust accounts to ensure they

stay on budget.

- · Posted, reviewed, and monitored accounts receivable and payable.
- Recorded and applied payments received on outstanding invoices.
- Reviewed and posted all invoices, bills and expenses in the accounting software

platform for TitleOne.

Posted daily revenue to daily report making sure report matched the accounting

software system.

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

Driver/Marketing Jul 2014 - Jul 2015 TitleOne Corporation, Boise, ID

 As the consumer facing business entity for title and escrow I was responsible for

the exchange of loan packages, title commitments, commission checks, listing packages and other related documents.

 Hand-deliver these items and establish positive rapport with existing clients in

efforts to both maintain and strengthen relationships.

• Sales Representative Sep 2013 - May 2014

Ace Hardware, Moscow, ID

• Worked with customers to determine purchasing needs and direct them to appropriate products to enhance service and satisfaction.

Seasonal Office Administrator Jan 2007 - Dec 2012 American Health Value, Boise, ID

- Coordinated with employees and customers on their Health Savings Accounts to maximize utilization of our services
- Researched and provided information for new clients and their healthcare needs.